rezv2000.com 2009-04-29

# Privacy Policy

Click here for our Terms of Use

## Our Privacy Policy

We take your privacy seriously. Earning and keeping your trust is important to us. We want you to understand what kinds of information we gather from you, how this information is used and protected, and how you can control its use. This statement discloses the privacy practices of Nutri Blvd. By using this website, you agree, without limitation or qualification, to be bound by this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy applies to the collection and use of information by Nutri Blvd on this website but does not apply to information that you may send to us by other means.

Any changes in our Privacy Policy will be communicated in this page so please check back from time to time.

### Who may use this website.

This website is not intended or designed to attract users under the age of 18. We do not collect personally identifiable data from any person we know to be under the age of 18 and instruct users under 18 not to send us any information. 

This site is restricted to users from the United States. Users from other countries are advised not to disclose personal information on this website. You transmit data to a server located in the State of Florida subject to United States and laws of the State of Florida. You should not send any personal information to this website unless you agree to be bound by United States and the law of the State of Florida.

### Information collected from you.

The kinds of information we collect from you will vary, depending on how you use our website. It's possible to browse our site without submitting any personal information at all. In order to take part in certain services on our website, you will be required to provide certain personal information (e.g., your name, address, e-mail address, etc.). 

In addition to the information you choose to submit, our systems are set up to gather certain anonymous data to help us better understand how our site is being used and how we can improve it. This automatically gathered data includes any content you view on our website.

### How your information is used.

We utilize "cookies" on our site. These are small files that we send to and store on your computer so that we may recognize it as a unique machine the next time you visit our site. Our cookies are used to let us know you are a prior customer and to help us personalize your online experience by providing you with advertisements and messages of interest to you. Also, companies offering products or services through our website may use their own cookies. 

The personal information you provide is used among other uses to help us customize your online experience. Your e-mail address serves as a unique identifier in our record system, and it is used together with a password to prevent unauthorized access to any information you choose to store on our site. The data you give us about your personal preferences and demographics (such as age, ZIP code, occupation, or other data) may be used to help us offer content, advertisements, products, and services that are most likely to appeal to you. 

We will use your personal information to respond to requests you may make of us, and from time to time, we may refer to such information to better understand your needs and how we can improve our website, products and services. We may also use this personal information to contact you and/or provide you with general health information (like information on certain health conditions). We may share this personal information with other companies who offer products and services that may be of interest to you. We may also enhance or merge this personal information with data obtained from third parties for the same purposes.

Unless you specify that you'd prefer not to hear from us, we may also use the e-mail address you provide at registration to contact you for promotional, administrative, or other reasons. You may have these communications terminated. This likely will take 48 hours from the time you give us notice.

The information gathered automatically by our system—such as your computer's IP address, the kind of browser you're using, and a record of your navigation through our site—may be used by us so we can understand how to make our site convenient and useful to our audience and to improve our products and services. 

We may link information collected from you through various means, including information collected automatically and through the use of cookies and personal information, with information we learn via Nutri Blvd Customer Care and from Rewards Program members. Our goal is to help offer you content, advertisements, products, and services that are most likely to appeal to you. 

### Your Choices Regarding the Use of Your Personal Information.

  * You can always choose not to provide personal information, even though it might be needed to take advantage of Nutri Blvd offers or website features. 
  * You can add or update certain information that you send to us. When you update information, we usually keep a copy of the prior version for our records. 
  * If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us or if you wish to check your personal information, please contact us by email to info@nutriblvd.com

### Access to Your Personal Information.

In the event that Nutri Blvd and some of our assets are sold or transferred or used as security, the personal information collected on our website may be transferred to third parties as part of that transaction. Nutri Blvd may also provide personal information or provide access to personal information to any of our affiliated businesses or to our business partners. 

Nutri Blvd may use your personal information to reply to you and send information to you. Nutri Blvd does not intend to reveal personal information to third parties except in the manner stated in this Privacy Policy. Nutri Blvd will provide aggregated information received from you to third parties. Nutri Blvd takes commercially reasonable precautions to prevent the aggregated information provided to third parties from including personal information.

If Nutri Blvd is requested by law enforcement officials or judicial authorities to provide personal information on individual users, Nutri Blvd may, without your consent, provide such information. In matters involving claims of personal or public safety or in litigation where the data is pertinent, Nutri Blvd may use or disclose your personal information without your consent or court process.

### Will Your Personal Information Be Secure?

Nutri Blvd recognizes you may be concerned about the security of your personal information, and we are committed to employing reasonable technology in order to protect the security of our website. Even with such technology, no website is 100% secure. We will take reasonable measures that we believe are appropriate to protect your information from loss, misuse, alteration or destruction, and, where possible, will ask that any third parties to whom we may transfer your information take comparable steps to protect that security. 

### Our Privacy Policy and Outside Links.

Our Privacy Policy only applies to this website. Our website contains links to sites outside our control. Please be aware that these sites may collect personal information about you, and operate according to their own privacy practices that may differ from our Privacy Policy. Remember to consult that website's own privacy policy, as once you're outside this website, any information you submit is no longer in our control. 

### Questions Regarding Our Privacy Policy.

If you have questions or comments regarding our privacy practices, please e-mail us at policy@nutriblvd.com

This policy was last updated on July 15th, 2008
